{"problemsArray": [
  {"answer": "4x^2 - 7x - 2", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(x)(4x) + (x)(1) + (-2)(4x) + (-2)(1)\n4x^2 + x - 8x - 2\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(x - 2) * (4x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-12x^2 - 21x - 9", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(4x)(-3x) + (4x)(-3) + (3)(-3x) + (3)(-3)\n-12x^2 - 12x - 9x - 9\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(4x + 3) * (-3x - 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10x^3 + 9x^2 + 6x + 2", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(5x^2)(2x) + (5x^2)(1) + (2x)(2x) + (2x)(1) + (2)(2x) + (2)(1)\n10x^3 + 5x^2 + 4x^2 + 2x + 4x + 2\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(5x^2 + 2x + 2) * (2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-25x^3 + 10x^2 + 40x + 15", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(5x^2)(-5x) + (5x^2)(-3) + (-5x)(-5x) + (-5x)(-3) + (-5)(-5x) + (-5)(-3)\n-25x^3 - 15x^2 + 25x^2 + 15x + 25x + 15\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(5x^2 - 5x - 5) * (-5x - 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x^2 - 11x - 6", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-3x)(x) + (-3x)(3) + (-2)(x) + (-2)(3)\n-3x^2 - 9x - 2x - 6\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-3x - 2) * (x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6x^2 + 4x - 10", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(3x)(2x) + (3x)(-2) + (5)(2x) + (5)(-2)\n6x^2 - 6x + 10x - 10\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(3x + 5) * (2x - 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5x^3 - 21x^2 + 19x - 3", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-x^2)(-5x) + (-x^2)(1) + (4x)(-5x) + (4x)(1) + (-3)(-5x) + (-3)(1)\n5x^3 - x^2 - 20x^2 + 4x + 15x - 3\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-x^2 + 4x - 3) * (-5x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x^3 - 5x^2 - 7x + 10", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-3x^2)(-x) + (-3x^2)(2) + (-x)(-x) + (-x)(2) + (5)(-x) + (5)(2)\n3x^3 - 6x^2 + x^2 - 2x - 5x + 10\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-3x^2 - x + 5) * (-x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x^2 - 15x - 25", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(4x)(x) + (4x)(-5) + (5)(x) + (5)(-5)\n4x^2 - 20x + 5x - 25\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(4x + 5) * (x - 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^3 - 5x^2 - 33x - 20", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-x^2)(-2x) + (-x^2)(-5) + (5x)(-2x) + (5x)(-5) + (4)(-2x) + (4)(-5)\n2x^3 + 5x^2 - 10x^2 - 25x - 8x - 20\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-x^2 + 5x + 4) * (-2x - 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-25x^3 - 5x^2 - 13x - 6", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-5x^2)(5x) + (-5x^2)(2) + (x)(5x) + (x)(2) + (-3)(5x) + (-3)(2)\n-25x^3 - 10x^2 + 5x^2 + 2x - 15x - 6\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-5x^2 + x - 3) * (5x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "15x^2 + x - 2", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(5x)(3x) + (5x)(-1) + (2)(3x) + (2)(-1)\n15x^2 - 5x + 6x - 2\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(5x + 2) * (3x - 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-8x^2 + 8", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(4x)(-2x) + (4x)(2) + (4)(-2x) + (4)(2)\n-8x^2 + 8x - 8x + 8\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(4x + 4) * (-2x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "20x^3 + 32x^2 + 32x + 20", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-5x^2)(-4x) + (-5x^2)(-4) + (-3x)(-4x) + (-3x)(-4) + (-5)(-4x) + (-5)(-4)\n20x^3 + 20x^2 + 12x^2 + 12x + 20x + 20\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-5x^2 - 3x - 5) * (-4x - 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-12x^3 - 11x^2 + 21x + 10", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-4x^2)(3x) + (-4x^2)(5) + (3x)(3x) + (3x)(5) + (2)(3x) + (2)(5)\n-12x^3 - 20x^2 + 9x^2 + 15x + 6x + 10\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-4x^2 + 3x + 2) * (3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "16x^3 - 32x^2 + 7x + 10", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(4x^2)(4x) + (4x^2)(-5) + (-3x)(4x) + (-3x)(-5) + (-2)(4x) + (-2)(-5)\n16x^3 - 20x^2 - 12x^2 + 15x - 8x + 10\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(4x^2 - 3x - 2) * (4x - 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-20x^2 - 28x - 8", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(5x)(-4x) + (5x)(-4) + (2)(-4x) + (2)(-4)\n-20x^2 - 20x - 8x - 8\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(5x + 2) * (-4x - 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-20x^3 - 28x^2 + 2x + 4", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(4x^2)(-5x) + (4x^2)(-2) + (4x)(-5x) + (4x)(-2) + (-2)(-5x) + (-2)(-2)\n-20x^3 - 8x^2 - 20x^2 - 8x + 10x + 4\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(4x^2 + 4x - 2) * (-5x - 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x^3 - 6x^2 - x + 2", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-3x^2)(x) + (-3x^2)(1) + (-3x)(x) + (-3x)(1) + (2)(x) + (2)(1)\n-3x^3 - 3x^2 - 3x^2 - 3x + 2x + 2\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-3x^2 - 3x + 2) * (x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5x^2 + 24x + 16", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-5x)(-x) + (-5x)(-4) + (-4)(-x) + (-4)(-4)\n5x^2 + 20x + 4x + 16\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-5x - 4) * (-x - 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5x^3 + 6x^2 - 28x + 16", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(x^2)(5x) + (x^2)(-4) + (2x)(5x) + (2x)(-4) + (-4)(5x) + (-4)(-4)\n5x^3 - 4x^2 + 10x^2 - 8x - 20x + 16\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(x^2 + 2x - 4) * (5x - 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5x^2 + 11x - 2", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(5x)(-x) + (5x)(2) + (-1)(-x) + (-1)(2)\n-5x^2 + 10x + x - 2\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(5x - 1) * (-x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x^2 + 8x + 3", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(3x)(-x) + (3x)(3) + (1)(-x) + (1)(3)\n-3x^2 + 9x - x + 3\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(3x + 1) * (-x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9x^2 + 3x - 12", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(3x)(3x) + (3x)(-3) + (4)(3x) + (4)(-3)\n9x^2 - 9x + 12x - 12\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(3x + 4) * (3x - 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5x^3 + 18x^2 - 24x + 9", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(x^2)(-5x) + (x^2)(3) + (-3x)(-5x) + (-3x)(3) + (3)(-5x) + (3)(3)\n-5x^3 + 3x^2 + 15x^2 - 9x - 15x + 9\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(x^2 - 3x + 3) * (-5x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9x^2 + 27x + 20", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(3x)(3x) + (3x)(4) + (5)(3x) + (5)(4)\n9x^2 + 12x + 15x + 20\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(3x + 5) * (3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "20x^2 - 9x + 1", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(4x)(5x) + (4x)(-1) + (-1)(5x) + (-1)(-1)\n20x^2 - 4x - 5x + 1\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(4x - 1) * (5x - 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-16x^3 - 36x^2 - 28x - 8", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-4x^2)(4x) + (-4x^2)(4) + (-5x)(4x) + (-5x)(4) + (-2)(4x) + (-2)(4)\n-16x^3 - 16x^2 - 20x^2 - 20x - 8x - 8\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-4x^2 - 5x - 2) * (4x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "15x^2 + 2x - 1", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(3x)(5x) + (3x)(-1) + (1)(5x) + (1)(-1)\n15x^2 - 3x + 5x - 1\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(3x + 1) * (5x - 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x^2 - 16", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-2x)(-2x) + (-2x)(4) + (-4)(-2x) + (-4)(4)\n4x^2 - 8x + 8x - 16\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-2x - 4) * (-2x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5x^3 + 8x^2 + 19x + 6", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-x^2)(5x) + (-x^2)(2) + (2x)(5x) + (2x)(2) + (3)(5x) + (3)(2)\n-5x^3 - 2x^2 + 10x^2 + 4x + 15x + 6\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-x^2 + 2x + 3) * (5x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8x^2 + 14x + 6", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(2x)(4x) + (2x)(3) + (2)(4x) + (2)(3)\n8x^2 + 6x + 8x + 6\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(2x + 2) * (4x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^2 - 15x + 25", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-2x)(-x) + (-2x)(5) + (5)(-x) + (5)(5)\n2x^2 - 10x - 5x + 25\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-2x + 5) * (-x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4x^3 - 5x^2 + 19x + 5", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(x^2)(-4x) + (x^2)(-1) + (x)(-4x) + (x)(-1) + (-5)(-4x) + (-5)(-1)\n-4x^3 - x^2 - 4x^2 - x + 20x + 5\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(x^2 + x - 5) * (-4x - 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-16x^2 - 12x + 10", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(4x)(-4x) + (4x)(-5) + (-2)(-4x) + (-2)(-5)\n-16x^2 - 20x + 8x + 10\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(4x - 2) * (-4x - 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-25x^3 - 6x - 9", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-5x^2)(5x) + (-5x^2)(3) + (3x)(5x) + (3x)(3) + (-3)(5x) + (-3)(3)\n-25x^3 - 15x^2 + 15x^2 + 9x - 15x - 9\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-5x^2 + 3x - 3) * (5x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-15x^3 - 2x^2 + 2x + 4", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(5x^2)(-3x) + (5x^2)(2) + (4x)(-3x) + (4x)(2) + (2)(-3x) + (2)(2)\n-15x^3 + 10x^2 - 12x^2 + 8x - 6x + 4\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(5x^2 + 4x + 2) * (-3x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "25x^2 - 20x + 3", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(5x)(5x) + (5x)(-1) + (-3)(5x) + (-3)(-1)\n25x^2 - 5x - 15x + 3\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(5x - 3) * (5x - 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5x^2 + 24x + 16", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-5x)(-x) + (-5x)(-4) + (-4)(-x) + (-4)(-4)\n5x^2 + 20x + 4x + 16\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-5x - 4) * (-x - 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x^3 - 13x^2 - 27x - 20", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(x^2)(-3x) + (x^2)(-4) + (3x)(-3x) + (3x)(-4) + (5)(-3x) + (5)(-4)\n-3x^3 - 4x^2 - 9x^2 - 12x - 15x - 20\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(x^2 + 3x + 5) * (-3x - 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^3 + 4x^2 - 10x - 12", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(x^2)(2x) + (x^2)(-4) + (4x)(2x) + (4x)(-4) + (3)(2x) + (3)(-4)\n2x^3 - 4x^2 + 8x^2 - 16x + 6x - 12\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(x^2 + 4x + 3) * (2x - 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3x^3 + 6x^2 - 7x + 6", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(3x^2)(x) + (3x^2)(3) + (-3x)(x) + (-3x)(3) + (2)(x) + (2)(3)\n3x^3 + 9x^2 - 3x^2 - 9x + 2x + 6\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(3x^2 - 3x + 2) * (x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "15x^2 + 7x - 4", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(3x)(5x) + (3x)(4) + (-1)(5x) + (-1)(4)\n15x^2 + 12x - 5x - 4\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(3x - 1) * (5x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-15x^2 + 8x + 16", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(3x)(-5x) + (3x)(-4) + (-4)(-5x) + (-4)(-4)\n-15x^2 - 12x + 20x + 16\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(3x - 4) * (-5x - 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10x^3 + 23x^2 + 37x + 20", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(2x^2)(5x) + (2x^2)(4) + (3x)(5x) + (3x)(4) + (5)(5x) + (5)(4)\n10x^3 + 8x^2 + 15x^2 + 12x + 25x + 20\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(2x^2 + 3x + 5) * (5x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "15x^2 + 13x - 20", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(3x)(5x) + (3x)(-4) + (5)(5x) + (5)(-4)\n15x^2 - 12x + 25x - 20\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(3x + 5) * (5x - 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6x^2 + 20x + 16", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-2x)(-3x) + (-2x)(-4) + (-4)(-3x) + (-4)(-4)\n6x^2 + 8x + 12x + 16\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-2x - 4) * (-3x - 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-12x^2 + 19x - 5", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(3x)(-4x) + (3x)(5) + (-1)(-4x) + (-1)(5)\n-12x^2 + 15x + 4x - 5\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(3x - 1) * (-4x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-8x^3 + 12x^2 + 30x - 25", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(4x^2)(-2x) + (4x^2)(5) + (4x)(-2x) + (4x)(5) + (-5)(-2x) + (-5)(5)\n-8x^3 + 20x^2 - 8x^2 + 20x + 10x - 25\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(4x^2 + 4x - 5) * (-2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9x^2 - 6x - 15", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(3x)(3x) + (3x)(3) + (-5)(3x) + (-5)(3)\n9x^2 + 9x - 15x - 15\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(3x - 5) * (3x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "25x^2 - 40x + 15", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(5x)(5x) + (5x)(-5) + (-3)(5x) + (-3)(-5)\n25x^2 - 25x - 15x + 15\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(5x - 3) * (5x - 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6x^3 - 2x^2 + 8x + 4", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-3x^2)(2x) + (-3x^2)(2) + (2x)(2x) + (2x)(2) + (2)(2x) + (2)(2)\n-6x^3 - 6x^2 + 4x^2 + 4x + 4x + 4\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-3x^2 + 2x + 2) * (2x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-12x^3 - 19x^2 - 13x - 12", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-4x^2)(3x) + (-4x^2)(4) + (-x)(3x) + (-x)(4) + (-3)(3x) + (-3)(4)\n-12x^3 - 16x^2 - 3x^2 - 4x - 9x - 12\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-4x^2 - x - 3) * (3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4x^2 - 4x + 8", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-4x)(x) + (-4x)(2) + (4)(x) + (4)(2)\n-4x^2 - 8x + 4x + 8\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-4x + 4) * (x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x^2 + 7x + 3", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(4x)(x) + (4x)(1) + (3)(x) + (3)(1)\n4x^2 + 4x + 3x + 3\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(4x + 3) * (x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x^2 - 10x + 4", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-2x)(-2x) + (-2x)(4) + (1)(-2x) + (1)(4)\n4x^2 - 8x - 2x + 4\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-2x + 1) * (-2x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2x^2 + 5x + 3", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-2x)(x) + (-2x)(-3) + (-1)(x) + (-1)(-3)\n-2x^2 + 6x - x + 3\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-2x - 1) * (x - 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-10x^2 + 8x + 2", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(2x)(-5x) + (2x)(-1) + (-2)(-5x) + (-2)(-1)\n-10x^2 - 2x + 10x + 2\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(2x - 2) * (-5x - 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-6x^3 + 12x^2 - 18x + 12", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-2x^2)(3x) + (-2x^2)(-3) + (2x)(3x) + (2x)(-3) + (-4)(3x) + (-4)(-3)\n-6x^3 + 6x^2 + 6x^2 - 6x - 12x + 12\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-2x^2 + 2x - 4) * (3x - 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5x^2 + 24x - 5", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-x)(-5x) + (-x)(1) + (-5)(-5x) + (-5)(1)\n5x^2 - x + 25x - 5\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-x - 5) * (-5x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6x^3 + 5x^2 + 3x + 1", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(3x^2)(2x) + (3x^2)(1) + (x)(2x) + (x)(1) + (1)(2x) + (1)(1)\n6x^3 + 3x^2 + 2x^2 + x + 2x + 1\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(3x^2 + x + 1) * (2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8x^2 + 18x + 9", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(2x)(4x) + (2x)(3) + (3)(4x) + (3)(3)\n8x^2 + 6x + 12x + 9\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(2x + 3) * (4x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10x^2 + 28x + 16", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(5x)(2x) + (5x)(4) + (4)(2x) + (4)(4)\n10x^2 + 20x + 8x + 16\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(5x + 4) * (2x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-15x^3 - 20x^2 - 8x - 1", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-5x^2)(3x) + (-5x^2)(1) + (-5x)(3x) + (-5x)(1) + (-1)(3x) + (-1)(1)\n-15x^3 - 5x^2 - 15x^2 - 5x - 3x - 1\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-5x^2 - 5x - 1) * (3x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-15x^3 - 22x^2 - 2x + 4", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-5x^2)(3x) + (-5x^2)(2) + (-4x)(3x) + (-4x)(2) + (2)(3x) + (2)(2)\n-15x^3 - 10x^2 - 12x^2 - 8x + 6x + 4\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-5x^2 - 4x + 2) * (3x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-15x^3 - 2x^2 - 8x - 3", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(5x^2)(-3x) + (5x^2)(-1) + (-x)(-3x) + (-x)(-1) + (3)(-3x) + (3)(-1)\n-15x^3 - 5x^2 + 3x^2 + x - 9x - 3\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(5x^2 - x + 3) * (-3x - 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-10x^2 - 15x - 5", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-2x)(5x) + (-2x)(5) + (-1)(5x) + (-1)(5)\n-10x^2 - 10x - 5x - 5\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-2x - 1) * (5x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-10x^2 - 23x + 5", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(5x)(-2x) + (5x)(-5) + (-1)(-2x) + (-1)(-5)\n-10x^2 - 25x + 2x + 5\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(5x - 1) * (-2x - 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2x^2 + x + 3", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(2x)(-x) + (2x)(-1) + (-3)(-x) + (-3)(-1)\n-2x^2 - 2x + 3x + 3\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(2x - 3) * (-x - 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "16x^3 + 8x^2 + x + 3", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-4x^2)(-4x) + (-4x^2)(-3) + (x)(-4x) + (x)(-3) + (-1)(-4x) + (-1)(-3)\n16x^3 + 12x^2 - 4x^2 - 3x + 4x + 3\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-4x^2 + x - 1) * (-4x - 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8x^3 - 14x^2 + 9x - 9", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(4x^2)(2x) + (4x^2)(-3) + (-x)(2x) + (-x)(-3) + (3)(2x) + (3)(-3)\n8x^3 - 12x^2 - 2x^2 + 3x + 6x - 9\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(4x^2 - x + 3) * (2x - 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2x^3 + 10x^2 - 2x - 6", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(x^2)(-2x) + (x^2)(2) + (-4x)(-2x) + (-4x)(2) + (-3)(-2x) + (-3)(2)\n-2x^3 + 2x^2 + 8x^2 - 8x + 6x - 6\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(x^2 - 4x - 3) * (-2x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5x^3 + 6x^2 - 3x + 2", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-5x^2)(x) + (-5x^2)(-1) + (x)(x) + (x)(-1) + (-2)(x) + (-2)(-1)\n-5x^3 + 5x^2 + x^2 - x - 2x + 2\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-5x^2 + x - 2) * (x - 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-25x^3 - 4x + 16", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-5x^2)(5x) + (-5x^2)(-4) + (-4x)(5x) + (-4x)(-4) + (-4)(5x) + (-4)(-4)\n-25x^3 + 20x^2 - 20x^2 + 16x - 20x + 16\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-5x^2 - 4x - 4) * (5x - 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-12x^2 + 4x + 8", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(3x)(-4x) + (3x)(4) + (2)(-4x) + (2)(4)\n-12x^2 + 12x - 8x + 8\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(3x + 2) * (-4x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x^3 + 7x^2 + 21x + 10", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(x^2)(-3x) + (x^2)(-2) + (-3x)(-3x) + (-3x)(-2) + (-5)(-3x) + (-5)(-2)\n-3x^3 - 2x^2 + 9x^2 + 6x + 15x + 10\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(x^2 - 3x - 5) * (-3x - 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5x^3 + 15x^2 + 35x + 15", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(x^2)(-5x) + (x^2)(-5) + (-4x)(-5x) + (-4x)(-5) + (-3)(-5x) + (-3)(-5)\n-5x^3 - 5x^2 + 20x^2 + 20x + 15x + 15\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(x^2 - 4x - 3) * (-5x - 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-12x^3 - 21x^2 - 21x - 9", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(3x^2)(-4x) + (3x^2)(-3) + (3x)(-4x) + (3x)(-3) + (3)(-4x) + (3)(-3)\n-12x^3 - 9x^2 - 12x^2 - 9x - 12x - 9\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(3x^2 + 3x + 3) * (-4x - 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2x^2 + 10x - 12", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-x)(2x) + (-x)(-4) + (3)(2x) + (3)(-4)\n-2x^2 + 4x + 6x - 12\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-x + 3) * (2x - 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x^2 + 6x + 2", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(x)(4x) + (x)(2) + (1)(4x) + (1)(2)\n4x^2 + 2x + 4x + 2\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(x + 1) * (4x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "20x^2 + x - 1", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-4x)(-5x) + (-4x)(1) + (-1)(-5x) + (-1)(1)\n20x^2 - 4x + 5x - 1\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-4x - 1) * (-5x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8x^2 - 18x + 10", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-4x)(-2x) + (-4x)(2) + (5)(-2x) + (5)(2)\n8x^2 - 8x - 10x + 10\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-4x + 5) * (-2x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^3 + 11x^2 + 9x + 2", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-x^2)(-2x) + (-x^2)(-1) + (-5x)(-2x) + (-5x)(-1) + (-2)(-2x) + (-2)(-1)\n2x^3 + x^2 + 10x^2 + 5x + 4x + 2\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-x^2 - 5x - 2) * (-2x - 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4x^3 + 6x^2 + 8x + 5", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(2x^2)(-2x) + (2x^2)(5) + (2x)(-2x) + (2x)(5) + (1)(-2x) + (1)(5)\n-4x^3 + 10x^2 - 4x^2 + 10x - 2x + 5\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(2x^2 + 2x + 1) * (-2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x^3 - 17x^2 - 25x - 20", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-3x^2)(x) + (-3x^2)(4) + (-5x)(x) + (-5x)(4) + (-5)(x) + (-5)(4)\n-3x^3 - 12x^2 - 5x^2 - 20x - 5x - 20\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-3x^2 - 5x - 5) * (x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4x^2 + 21x + 20", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(x)(4x) + (x)(5) + (4)(4x) + (4)(5)\n4x^2 + 5x + 16x + 20\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(x + 4) * (4x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-5x^3 - 5x^2 + 13x + 6", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-5x^2)(x) + (-5x^2)(2) + (5x)(x) + (5x)(2) + (3)(x) + (3)(2)\n-5x^3 - 10x^2 + 5x^2 + 10x + 3x + 6\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-5x^2 + 5x + 3) * (x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^3 - x^2 - 16x - 15", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-x^2)(-2x) + (-x^2)(-3) + (2x)(-2x) + (2x)(-3) + (5)(-2x) + (5)(-3)\n2x^3 + 3x^2 - 4x^2 - 6x - 10x - 15\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-x^2 + 2x + 5) * (-2x - 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-2x^3 + 4x^2 + 11x - 15", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(2x^2)(-x) + (2x^2)(3) + (2x)(-x) + (2x)(3) + (-5)(-x) + (-5)(3)\n-2x^3 + 6x^2 - 2x^2 + 6x + 5x - 15\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(2x^2 + 2x - 5) * (-x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2x^2 + 3x - 9", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-x)(-2x) + (-x)(3) + (-3)(-2x) + (-3)(3)\n2x^2 - 3x + 6x - 9\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-x - 3) * (-2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x^3 + 8x^2 - 6x + 1", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(3x^2)(-x) + (3x^2)(1) + (-5x)(-x) + (-5x)(1) + (1)(-x) + (1)(1)\n-3x^3 + 3x^2 + 5x^2 - 5x - x + 1\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(3x^2 - 5x + 1) * (-x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-16x^2 - 16x - 3", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(4x)(-4x) + (4x)(-1) + (3)(-4x) + (3)(-1)\n-16x^2 - 4x - 12x - 3\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(4x + 3) * (-4x - 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-15x^3 + 31x^2 + 5x - 25", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-5x^2)(3x) + (-5x^2)(-5) + (2x)(3x) + (2x)(-5) + (5)(3x) + (5)(-5)\n-15x^3 + 25x^2 + 6x^2 - 10x + 15x - 25\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-5x^2 + 2x + 5) * (3x - 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6x^2 - 10x - 4", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(2x)(3x) + (2x)(1) + (-4)(3x) + (-4)(1)\n6x^2 + 2x - 12x - 4\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(2x - 4) * (3x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3x^3 + 20x^2 - 10x - 25", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-x^2)(3x) + (-x^2)(-5) + (5x)(3x) + (5x)(-5) + (5)(3x) + (5)(-5)\n-3x^3 + 5x^2 + 15x^2 - 25x + 15x - 25\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-x^2 + 5x + 5) * (3x - 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8x^3 + 10x^2 - 23x + 5", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(4x^2)(2x) + (4x^2)(5) + (-5x)(2x) + (-5x)(5) + (1)(2x) + (1)(5)\n8x^3 + 20x^2 - 10x^2 - 25x + 2x + 5\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(4x^2 - 5x + 1) * (2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4x^2 + 10x - 6", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(-2x)(2x) + (-2x)(-3) + (2)(2x) + (2)(-3)\n-4x^2 + 6x + 4x - 6\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(-2x + 2) * (2x - 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "20x^2 + 21x + 4", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(4x)(5x) + (4x)(4) + (1)(5x) + (1)(4)\n20x^2 + 16x + 5x + 4\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(4x + 1) * (5x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-10x^2 - 23x + 5", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(5x)(-2x) + (5x)(-5) + (-1)(-2x) + (-1)(-5)\n-10x^2 - 25x + 2x + 5\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(5x - 1) * (-2x - 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4x^3 - 23x^2 + x + 12", "explanation": "Multiply each term of the second polynomial by each term in the first\n(x^2)(-4x) + (x^2)(-3) + (5x)(-4x) + (5x)(-3) + (-4)(-4x) + (-4)(-3)\n-4x^3 - 3x^2 - 20x^2 - 15x + 16x + 12\nCombine like-terms", "question": "Multiply:\n(x^2 + 5x - 4) * (-4x - 3)", "type": "text"}
]}